<resources>
    <string name="setup_title_welcome">welcome to mercurius</string>
    <string name="setup_welcome">Welcome to the setup wizard for the login service.
        In The following steps the basic configurations for the service are carried out.

        After you have accepted the license agreements and made the necessary
        configurations, the wizard initializes and starts the login service for your
        environment.

        After completion, it is possible to create users with different clients and
        initialize sessions for them.

        You can retun to the previous steps at any time to make adjustments to your settings.
    </string>
    <string name="setup_title_license">license</string>
    <string name="setup_license">worldiety Enterprise Edition (EE) License (the "EE License")
        Copyright (c) 2020 worldiety GmbH

        This software and the associated documentation may only be used if you or the natural
        or legal entity you represent, have a corresponding individual agreement with the worldiety GmbH
        about the use of this software. Unless otherwise agreed, you have, after the completion of all outstanding payments,
        a non-exclusive, worldwide, perpetual and irrevocable right to use the software. In addition, you are granted
        permission, in accordance with the agreements made, to use the software and publish patches for the software.
        In doing so, you agree that worldiety receives an exclusive, worldwide, unlimited and irrevocable right of use of
        the modifications. This also applies in particular to commissioned modifications, which are carried out by third
        parties or by worldiety within the scope of service or contracts for work and services arise.

        You are not permitted to copy, merge or combine this software as an independent product,
        to publish, distribute, sublicense or sell Deviating from this. Unaffected is your permission to copy, distribute,
        sublicense or sell this software as auxiliary or accessory of your software product.

        Used components of third parties, which are integrated into the worldiety software, remain under the respective
        Original license of the respective licensor.</string>

    <string name="btn_next">next</string>
    <string name="btn_accept">accept</string>
</resources>